本字幕由夜桜字幕組制作
翻譯:お兄様
時軸                  晚風
校對                  雪夜
壓制                        物菌
今日 深深夜幕如往常一樣降臨江戶 對著鏡子抹上口紅
有求必應 逆來順受
那閃著橙色光芒的花朵 我曾憧憬過 也曾渴求過
不知何時 已變成藍色的花 可是我啊 也沒有這么廉價
其實我本想要做一朵只為一人綻放的花朵 然而命運卻奪取了我的自由 它的齒輪將我無情的碾碎
這充滿虛假的戀愛 你便要就這樣擁抱我嗎
我拼命假裝我能感覺到你 這是多么悲傷 今日的吉原 在下雨
這位大人 你能否就這樣將我買下呢
夾雜在紛紛綻放的雨傘之中 渾身濕透的我 不就像雨一樣嗎
車水馬龍的行人 此起彼伏的吆喝 互相吸引 互舔傷痕
我的心愿只有一個 誰能有朝一日 將我帶出這個鳥籠
其實我早已經無處可歸 可是這鳥籠中看見的風景 卻不知何時成了我僅有的慰藉
充滿虛假的戀愛 你便要這樣買下我嗎
綻放在我身上的花朵 降臨在我那濕透的心上 正是雨啊
大人請你與我 沉浸于這僅限一夜的歡愉中吧
而這些 褶皺一道一道 都鈍鈍地 刺痛了我的心
染著憂郁的花朵 渴求著枯萎了 「歡迎光臨」
玩著戀人游戲的那些夜晚 喘息著發出「啊啊」的聲音
我拼命裝作能感受到你 這是多么的悲傷 今日的吉原 心中仍然下著雨
充滿虛假的戀愛 便要如此擁抱我嗎
我拼命假裝我能感受到你 這是多么的悲傷 今日的吉原仍然下著雨
這位大人請問你能否買下我
夾雜在紛紛綻放的雨傘中 渾身濕透的我 不就像雨一樣嗎
Ayane.這次叫你來 是有一件很重要的任務給你.
Ayane. I called you today, to entrust you with a very important task.
一艘從英屬東印度出發的船就要到了，下個月它就要返回歐洲.
A ship from the British concession in India is coming soon. Next month, it will go back to Europe.
我愿為師傅您赴湯蹈火
I would do anything for you, Master.
你要利用這個時間救出rose大小姐
You are going to use that time to save Rose O Jiao Sama
我們的領袖在15年前的政變中被打敗了
Our master was defeated during the political struggle 15 years ago.
從那時起，所有的有識之士都受到了打壓。我們現在能做的只有把他女兒送去歐洲。
And anyone holding enlightened ideal are repressed everywhere. For now, all we can do is send his daughter to Europe.
我馬上動身前往吉原
I'm leaving for Yoshiwara right away.
愿犧牲同志們的在天之靈保佑你
Might the spirits of our death help you on your way.
臭老頭.每次都說這么瘆人的話.
Tsch. Old Geezer. You say these horrifying words every time.
我剛看到你說的那個男人去了旁邊的窯子.
I just saw the man you mentioned, going into the brothel nearby.
他不會這樣對我的，這不可能。
He can't do to me. That's impossible.
快看，他出來了，你的小心肝，我說什么來著。
Look, he's coming out. That's your Johnny. What did I tell you ?
小兔崽子
siiiiiiii～～～～whelp
男人來到吉原都是為了一時尋歡作樂
Men come to Yoshiwara just for a moment of fun.
是我太年輕了.我不會在信他們鬼話了.
I was too young to know better. I wont believe them again.
他們可以對隨便一晚對別的女孩說同樣的甜言蜜語。
They can tell the same sweet words to any girl on any other night.
我會牢記在心的，Kasumi姐姐大人。
I will keep that in mind. Kasumi onesama.
如果有人愿意贖我之身.將我帶離這吉原苦海.我愿將我的一切交付于他.
If there is any men willing to redeem me, to take me outside theses high walls, I would give my heart to him.
Nyotengu恢復了嗎？
Has Nyotengu recovered from yesterday ?
哎，管他的，把她弄來
I don't care. Make her come.
是，Daiki大人。
Yes, Daiki sama.
很高興看到你的身體恢復了，這樣你就能享受今天的樂子。
I am pleased to see your body has recovered from yesterday, so you can enjoy today's program.
晚上好 Daikia大人
Good evening Daiki sama
先生們，感謝大家今晚的出席。我為剛剛的小推遲道歉。我今晚邀請了新的調教師，他們將展示大家期待已久的特殊技巧。現在，讓我們開始表演。
Gentlemen. Thank you all for your presence.
我今晚邀請了新的調教師，他們將展示大家期待已久的特殊技巧。現在，讓我們開始表演。
And I apologize for that small delay. For this show, tonight, I invited new tormentor. They will show their special skills that everyone is awaiting this. Now, Let's start the show.
咕嘿嘿，聽說你是吉原的名妓
Wow, heard you are a Yoshiwara lorette?
真是個好屁股
That's a good butt.
我有點小失望啊，你拿著杯子這么不小心.
I am a little disappointed, you aren't more careful with glasses.
快過去和客人們道歉
Go ahead and apologize to the guest
快點 ，別讓客人們生氣
Hurry .Before the guests get angry
小女女天狗.遲到了還打碎了大人們的酒杯.我真的非常抱歉.我會用我的身體作為補償.
I'm Nyotengu. I apologize for being late and breaking your glasses. I'll use my chest as a replacement.
我愿大家可以享受這場性宴
I wish you all enjoy this show
既然你打碎了杯子.那就用自己身體為客人們敬酒吧.
Now that you've broken the glass, use your breasts as a cup to serve the guests.
乖女孩.果然被調教的不錯
Good girl. She was well trained.
漂亮.下一個客人.
Well done. Who's next ?
輪到我了！看這多汁的大奶子
It's my turn! Just look at those juicy boobs.
別停下.下一個
Don't stop. Next one
起來.喂到客人嘴里
Get up. Pour it into the guest's mouth
讓我們趕緊進入下一個環節!
Now let's move into our next segment！
嘿！天狗 你他媽的張嘴
Hi. Nyotengu open your fucking mouth
這些夠了么？
Is that enough?
再來點.今天到場的客人多.我們需要加大藥量
Give her some more. There are more guests today. We need more medicine.
都吞下去！這些藥會很起作用的
Swallow it all down ! This drug should be very effective.
超級見效。
Very useful
忍住！天狗女士。
Hold it. Lady Nyotengu.
超級見效。
Very useful
什么事？客人先生
What's the matter, Mister !
你們給她灌了什么藥？
What drug did you make her take ?
啊！這個啊 您自己看吧
Oh! We are giving her this.
空孕催乳劑！這藥很牛逼
thuocduame ！This medicine is magical.
哈哈哈 你感覺到了胸部劇烈的脹痛了吧？
Hahaha. Do you feel your chest aching and stretching ?
感覺爽爆了吧？對吧？
You're feeling pretty good right now, aren't you ?
直起腰來！讓客人們可以看到你那發騷表情.
Rise up ! Let our guests see the face you are making.
哦，請幫···啊···
Oh, please help... it's...ah
慢慢揉你的大奶子  讓藥力完全發揮
Rub your boobs. Slowly. Let the drug fully play.
快看 她的奶子在膨脹！
Look. Her boobs are expanding.
這是怎么回事
What is this.
有奶射出來了
She's leaking milk !
你要摸我嗎？
Are you going to touch me?
大家不必客氣.如果你不幫她把奶都吸出來.她就會一直這么難受下去
Please help yourself. She will be in a terrible pain if you don't help her suck the milk out.
請大家幫我把奶水吸出來.
Please help me suck it out.
我感激不盡
I would be very grateful.
嘿，我們用這個吸奶器把奶吸出來
Hey,let's use this breast pump to quickly suck out the milk.
今晚很多客人不喝奶，所以我為你準備了這個小道具
There are many guests here do not drink milk, so I prepared this prop for your
看啊，好像在海綿里擠水，奶子都吸出來了
Look, it;s like squeezing the sponge, look these cuts are being squeezed out.
我會努力侍奉大家，所以求你們，把你們的大屌插進我欲求不滿的穴里
I'll try to serve everyone... So please... Stick your cocks inside my insatiable pussy.
有請女狗進入淫欲之池
Lady Nyotengu. Please enter the erotic pool.
填滿我，把我當你們的RBQ
and fill me up... Like your personal cum bucket...
為什么你的小屄已經這么濕嗒嗒得了？
Why is your pussy so wet ?
因為我想要一些大家伙插我的騷屄
Because, it want something big to plug it in.
別玩弄我了.快拿大雞巴插我吧
Don't torture me. Just give to me.
哦，這是...
What is this...
小妞 快看 我已經勃起貯備好了
Mistress. Look. I am erect and ready.
這么大，我從沒見過這么大的，這不可能，好大的屌啊
Such a big... I've never seen anything like this. It's impossible. What a dick!
哇哦 感覺真棒. 肏啊 里面又濕潤有光滑.
It feels so good!! FUCK! She's so wet and slippery.
哈哈哈哈 .我愛這個騷穴. 這不愧是名妓啊
hahahahha. I love this pussy. she is definitely a good lorette
日本真是個享受的好國度，“特色產業”充滿了騷女人
Japan is a such great country for leisure. The "special industry" is plentiful with lewd woman.
大輝大人 我會繼續努力的.請繼續看著我
Daika-sama! I will continue doing my best. Please keep looking at me.
綻放你全部的魅力. 你現在看起來美麗極了
You're radiating all your charm. At this moment, you are at your most beautiful.
小姐，你剛剛高潮了？可夜晚才剛剛開始呢.
Mistress, did you just came ? By the night is just about to begin.
我們還要做很多很多愛呢
We have a lot of lovemaking to do.
我的腦子一片空白了
My mind has  gone completely blank.
我忍不住了. 你一對大奶子在我面前晃來晃去的
I could hold it any longer. Your tits are too enticing when they bounces in front me.
給我，給我
Please give me all your comes mister.
請看著我
Please look at me, ahhh
這次邀請的調教師都好厲害
The invited tormentor are very strong this time.
看來今晚的表演會很出色
It looks like this show be wonderful.
我射了
I'm coming.
啊 我大腿的屄穴里面都已經麻木了 哦 不要了
Ah. My thighs and pussy are already numb. Oh no.
我要休息下
I've got to rest.
哈哈哈 果然名不虛傳.
You got a really well-deserved reputation.
你比別的女人緊多了
You're tighter than other.
她是我操過的最好的女人
She's the best women I've ever fucked in my life
臥槽
Fucking me
等我球再次充滿.我在他娘的干你一炮
Wait until my ball are full again. I will meet you there.
我怎么操你都不夠啊 Nyotengu
I'll never get tired of fucking you . Nyotengu!
你出了那么多的汗. 得補充點水分啊  小姐
You're sweating a lot. Have a drink mistress.
酒精可以讓你更加容易的釋放你本性  沉迷在性愛的快樂中
Alcohol can help you indulge yourself more in the pleasure of sex
好爽 干的漂亮 女天狗
It feels so good Nyotengu. You did well.
到你了 兄弟
Now, that's your turn bro!
干我!
I need more!
我們會用精液填滿你的淫穴....一個接著一個的肏死你
Strange, we've been filling your pussy... one after one.
按住她的胳膊. 灌更多的酒 這樣她就會癱成一坨泥 任由我們擺弄
Hold her arm down. Pour more wine for her. Her body will be defenseless against our assault.
夫人 你喜歡這些大雞巴對吧？群奸最適合你了
Mistress. You love this, right ? I bet you do. A gangbang is the best for you.
肏了他兄弟 狠狠的插她  哈哈
do it dude. pound her hard haha
這個體位，啊，好羞恥
This position, ah em , embarrassing
我想她是被肏傻了她肯定超級爽
She's been fuck dumb. She must be very happy
對  填滿她 填滿她騷屄
Fill her up! Fill her cunt!
我想讓你繼續肏我 肏死我  我想要更多大雞巴 我要大雞巴
I want this to go on... I want more... I need more...
感覺太爽了
This feels so good.
我要拓展你的小穴
I'm going to stretch your pussy wide.
不要停止操我
Don`t stop
我愛你的大雞巴. 插爆我
I want your big cock!!! shove your huge dick inside me!
狠狠的插我！對的 射吧
thrust it deep!!Yeah. Do it please
你想讓我內射你么？  快回答我！
you want my cum inside you?   answer me!!
射吧 射進來 射進來
Do it. Cum inside me!
操！我要射了！接好了！
Fuck! I'm about to cum!!!! Take it allllll!!!!!
操的很爽吧？精液都從你的騷穴里溢出來了
It's good right？ all this semen oozing from your pussy.
恩？啊啊啊！！別打我的屁股
hum~~ahhh!!!! Don't hit my ass
你喝多了 .得清醒清醒了
You drank too much. We need to sober you up.
感覺好點了么？\VDo you feel better?
她被操傻了，除了雞巴什么都說不出來
She's been fuck dumb. She can't speak about anything else but dick.
我要射了，我要射了
I'm gonna cum!!! I'm gonna cum!!!
你想讓我們射到哪里？
Where do you want us to cum?
我也不知道
I don't know
想射哪射哪
Come wherever you want
進來吧
coming
一天后
好的
Ok
有什么我需要知道的重要事情嗎？
Is there anything important I need to know ?
這么早打擾您 我很抱歉 我想為一個吉原妓女贖身
Sorry to disturb you so early. I would have a prostitute from Yoshiwara freed.
就是你經常去的那家妓院的妓女嗎？
Is she from that brothel you go so often ?
是的 我都想帶她離開吉原
Yes. i want to take her away from Yoshiwara.
我知道我提出這樣的要求非常的魯莽
I am aware I am asking you a very reckless request.
但是我真心希望她可以從此改變命運
But I really hope she has the chance to change her fate.
什么樣的女人能讓你如此著迷.她名字是什么？
What kind of woman can make you so fascinated？What's her name
當然了，她叫做 瑪麗羅斯
Of course! She is called Marie Rose.
她和羅斯家族什么關系
What is her relationship with the Rose family ?
前任內閣大臣的女兒
She is the daughter of the former cabinet minister
我可真沒想到她居然會流落到了yoshiwara.如果你說的都是真的,這道挺有意思
I would never have expected her to fall to Yoshiwara. This sparks my interest. If it's true.
那么？
So what do you think ?
15年前那次政變的確改變了日本歷史.我可以贖她離開吉原.但是是作為我自己的小妾
That coup, 15 years ago, indeed changed the history of Japan. I'll accept your request. I'll make her leave Yoshiwara. But as my concubine.
什么！？
What ? Sorry.
我提醒你武士特權已經被廢止了.你現在只是普通百姓.I remind you that samurai privilege are abolished. There is only civilians now.
謝謝  Daiki大人  我清楚自己的身份
Thank you Daiki sama. I understand my rank very well.
啊？春馬？？？
Ah  Haruma？？？
是大輝？？ 他來這里干什么？就是這個男人娶走了Nyotengu
Daiki!!! What is he doing here ? That man is married to Nyotengu.
想為maire rose贖身？ 不是剛給Nyotengu贖身了么？大輝大人真是出手闊綽.這些錢可是給花魁Nyotengu級別贖身所需的資費啊
You want to purchase Marie Rose contract ? But you just redeemed Nyotengu. You are very generous Daiki-sama. This offering is on the same level as the one you did for Nyotengu.
但 rose只是普通級別的藝妓.我們非常感激您
But Nyotengu is an Oiran and Rose is just a common Geiko. We are very grateful.
我喜歡混血女孩
ah ha.  I like half-breed girl.
那么就有請Daiki大人驗貨吧
So, Daiki-sama, if you would like to inspect her.
rose 不知道你怎么這么幸運被大輝大人選中，其他女孩都巴不得和你一樣。
Rose, I don't know why you're so lucky. It's a chance to be selected by Daiki-sama. The other girls wish to be in your place.
沒問題吧. 我們老大可是花了大價錢把她買走的
She is allowed to come with us. Our boss has already paid for her contract.
看看這筆交易
Here,  look at this deal.
終身擁有她
Own her permanent.
每一天我都幻想著. 幻想著可以邁出吉原的大門
Everyday, I have been thinking about it. About crossing the Yoshwara gates.
這一天終于到來了
At last, the day has come.
我手下不會跟著我們了，以為等下要去的是個秘密地點
My men won't be escorting us there. Because the next room is a secret area.
這是大輝大人的私人住所？
Is this Daika-sama Private quarters ?
別著急. 你一會就都知道了.我15年前見過你，你現在出落成大美女了
Don't worry. You'll know everything in a moment. I saw you 15 years ago. You've grown up into such a beauty.
大輝大人，我們從前見過？
Say.  Daika-sama. Have we met before ?
這是什么？
ah???   What is it?
色究竟天
Akanistha
這是什么聲音？
What's that noise?
女天狗？！
Nyotengu!!!
我簡直不敢相信我看到的這一切
I can't be believe what I am seeing with my own eyes.
你們在干嘛？
What are you doing?
超爽的
so good
你騙了我
You tricked me.
哈哈哈哈哈 這不是顯而易見么？rose 大小姐
Hahaha. It should have been obvious. Miss Rose.
你真可惡，什么叫顯而易見？你不是娶了Nyotengu么？為什么還讓她做這種事情？
You are awful. What do you mean, obvious ? You're married with Nyotengu ! Why did she have to do this ?
哈哈哈哈 真幼稚，娶她為妻？你們只是妓女.這是一生都抹不去的污點.
So Naive. Married with her ? You are just prostitutes. It's a stain that you can never get rid of.
別碰我，滾開
Don't touch me! Knock it off !
再說了，幫助男人發泄肉欲不就是妓女的工作么？
And, in the end. Isn't it a prostitute job's to help man vent their desires ?
別逼我.你這個人渣
Don't make me swear at you, you piece of shit!
臭婊子   居然敢打我，你他媽的，你脾氣和你爸一樣倔
You little cunt! You dare hit ME!!! Fuck you. Your temper is as stubborn as your father.
你打女人？
You would hit a woman ?!
女人？不不不.你只是妓女而已.妓女除了服侍男人其他的什么也都不會做.你這從小被賣到妓院的 什么都不懂啊
Woman? Hehe. No, you're just a prostitute. Prostitutes have no right except to serve men. For someone was raised into a brothel since childhood, you don't know a thing.
走出吉原一點用都沒有
Going out of Yoshiwara won't do you any good.
你這么瞧不起妓女.為什么幫我們贖身！
If you think so lowly of prostitudes, why do you help us out ?
幫你們？不不不，這只是生意，以前還要帶著這些外國客人去Yoshiwara.現在只要把他們帶來我的城堡
既省錢 還沒有那么多規矩，只要那些客人聽說是Yoshiwara的妓女.就會更加的興致勃勃
Help you ? No it's for business. I had to make my foreign guest to Yoshiwara before. Now I'll just invite them to my palace. I am saving money and I don't have to follow the traditional code of conduct. And as long as my guest know you are former Yoshiwara prostitutes, they are delighted.
臥槽，真他媽人渣
What a scumbag.
人面獸心
You're a demon in human shape.
我不管你怎么說,已經沒有任何的意義了,
你最好先考慮下自己現在是什么立場,只要我手里有這個賣身契.你就得任由我擺布！
I don't care about what you are saying. It doesn't matter now. You'd better know your place. As long as I have your contract, you are at my mercy.
我不要. 請把我送回去
I don't to do that. Please send me back.
你行嗎？來試試啊！
Can you, go ahead and try.
把它給我！
Contract！
啊 哈～～～你們要干什么？？？啊 啊～～～
What are you doing?ha~~~ha~~~
瑪麗羅斯，既然你已經無力反抗.不如就坦然的接受這個現實吧
Now that you can't go back, it's better for you to accept your new life.
我絕不
Never
金魚離開水是活不下去的
A goldfish can't survive without water.
老頭子. 這次任務可不簡單啊
You haven't given me an easy mission, old man.
但是我絕不退縮
But I won't flater from it.
這里死人了！！這個刺客是誰
Somebody died here!!! Who is this assassin ?
去死吧！到這來，Rose 大小姐
Go to hell !!! Die !!! Come here Rose o  jiao sama.
操，別殺我
fuck！！！Don't kill me
滾開！人渣，
get out!!!Scumbag.
我們現在必須馬上離開.一會在跟您解釋，恩？操NWe must get away right now. I'll explain everything to you later. shit~~
小心背后
Watch your back
快跑
Quick, run
等下，你是？
Wait (ha ha), who are ?
別叫他們跑了.抓住他們
Don't let them escape! Capture them.
糟糕！ 請呆在這里 rose大小姐 等我先殺了他們
We're out of luck. Stay here Rose ojiao sama. Wait for me until I kill them all!
大家小心這婊子可狠毒了
Everyone be careful！！！This bitch is ferocious.
別當我路.擋路者死！
Get out of my way, or die !
你剛才說什么，婊子？
What did you just say bitch ?
哦，這女的可真不錯
Oh, that girl, she is such a babe.
來吧 婊子
come on!Bitch!!!
臥槽  太快了
fuck！she's too fast.
別抵抗了，我去，我的腳！你個賤人
stop resisting! ahhh! My feet, ahhh bitch!!
曹尼瑪
fuck you
閉嘴吧！
Shut the fuck up
求你了 別殺我，我下周就要結婚了
Please!! Don't kill me. I am going to marry next week.
那可真是遺憾
Sorry about that.
來人啊！！！擋住她啊。蒼馬你來的正好
Someone !!! Block her way out. Soma. You've come right on time. Stop that assassin.
好的 就去
Yes, yes coming on my way
春馬！春馬！
閉嘴 賤人
Shut Up bitch
看看你都做了些什么
Look at what you did.
你這個瘋狂的殺人魔！！！
You're a maniac and a murderer !!!!
別擋我的路！去死，滾開
Don't put yourself between me and rose !!! Die!!! Yaaaa!! Yaaaa!! Get out of my way!
嘗嘗我劍術的滋味 薬丸自顕流 蒼馬參上
Taste the slash of my sword Yakuruarugi labyrinth‘s soma Debut
薬丸自顕流？那不是護衛羅斯家族的武士們嗎
Yakuruagi Labyrinth ? Aren't you from the samura clan that guarded the Rose Family ?
接好了 這終極一擊
Take this, ultimate blow!
你怎么能這樣 你個叛徒！
How dare you ! Traitor !
干的漂亮 蒼馬.
Well done !!! soma
你做到了！她完了
Wow man you did it. She is finished.
你下手怎么能這么狠
How dare you attacking us in your mansion ?\
你知道你殺了多少人嗎？
Do you know how many you have killed?
放開我
let me go
她還以為自己能安然離開
She though she was going to get away with this.
老實點
You behave yourself!
不 不 不 不要···
no no
大輝大人
大輝大人 這邊請
this way daikisama
大輝大人
感謝您的光臨
How nice of you to come.
審的怎么樣了
Are you progressing with her interrogation ?
她什么都沒說。
She didn't say anything
她當然什么都不會說了.你上來就塞住了她的嘴巴.
She certainly won't say anything. You plugged her mouth. You're torturing her only for your pleasure.
你他媽的給我閉嘴。
Fucking shut you up!!!
我只是實話實說。
I just like to tell it how it is bro.
那你怎么不說你的方法都沒用？
Then why don't you say that every methods you tried failed ?
至少我的方法能讓她說話
At least, my method COULD have her talk.
你們兩個廢物. 都是廢物
Shut up. You are as bad as each other.
蒼馬呢？
Where is Soma?
蒼馬說他不愿意干這么卑鄙的事情.
Soma said he didn't want to something so despicable.
他不在還好了
It's better that he isn't here.
讓我看看你的臉.你叫什么？
Let me look at your face. What's your name?
我們老板問你話呢.回話
Our boss is asking you !!!answer
這是唯一線索.
This is our only clue about her.
暗影獵狐部落 Rose家族的殘黨
A Shadow Fox clan mask... They are from the rose family.
啊 不愧是老大 .分分鐘解開了謎題
Ah! That is our boss. Always finding the solution.
事情很嚴重，這背后肯定有個組織
It's very serious. There must be an organization behind this Kunoichi.
找到她的老巢,老頭子還活著
Find her den. That old man must be still alive
對不起.雖然我討厭使用暴力手段對待一個可愛的女孩
Sorry. Although I don't want to use violence against a cute girl
但是你好像惹怒了Daki sama
But you seem to have angered Daiki SAMA
而且讓你開口能給我帶來獎金
I also want to get a reward from making you talk.
如果你能老實交代的話.我們會獎勵你
If you answer honestly, we'll be sure to reward you.
把她拉過來
Bring her over here.
把她抓緊別讓她掙扎，我要一路開發進去，看她能撐多久
Hold it steady and don't let her struggle, I'm gonna open her all the way, see how long she can last.
她已經在抽動了 她要高潮了
She's already twitching, she's going to spring.
你高潮得可真快 你雖然是個殺手 但你畢竟是個女人
You are ejaculation so soon, although you are a assassin but you are still a women after all
你胳膊酸了么？換我把？
Aren't you getting your arm tired ? Do you want to switch ?
我讓很多女人哭著求饒 不過我還是第一次把這一套用在你這樣強硬的女人身上
I've made a lot of woman weep, but it is the first time I've done it with a woman as strong as you.
她現在心里很清楚 屈服是遲早的事情
She is very moast. It's only a matter of time before she give in.
在你親口同意之前.我們是不會給你的
We won't give you one until you fully agree to it though.
我猜你肯定有操守吧 呵呵
Guess you have some principles right hehehe
好了 換我上
OK Switch with me now.
這水車會確保你不再昏過去
This wheel will make sure you don't faint again
草泥馬.她的確不會暈倒了.我感覺我們兩個快暈倒了
Fuck you. It's not her who is going to faint. It's us by turning this wheel.
她就要崩潰了
Maybe she's going to clasp.
我們也要崩了 你他媽停下
Well, we also are going to. Just fucking stop.
我知道你是女忍者
I know you're a Kunoichi.
你接受過嚴格的訓練 但我們有錢有勢
And that you have been trained rigorously. But your enemy is rich and powerful
有錢不能是你們為所欲為
Money doesn't allow you to do whatever you want !
不不不 你低估了錢的能力 給她加刑.看看她還能堅持多久
Sorry. But you really underestimate the power of money. Punish her more. Let see how much long she can hold.
從那一刻起.我徹底崩潰了 我把我知道的都告訴了他們
From that moment, I was devastated. I told them everything they wanted to know.
他們很快的找到了深山中的巢穴
They quicky found the den, deep inside the montains.
師傅.請原諒我
master Please forgive me
我沒能完成您的遺愿,，羅斯先生
Sorry, I failed to complete your last wish, Master Rose.
我們回去領賞吧
Let's go back and collect our reward.
這兩女孩怎么辦？殺了她們？
What's about these girls ? Shall we kill them ?
你真要殺了這兩個可愛的小姐姐？ 你咋改主意了？（猥瑣臉
Are you really able to kill those cuties ? Why did you change your mind?
我想到有比殺死她們更殘忍的方法
I think there are more cruel ways than killing them
如果面具下是一張丑陋的臉呢？
What if there is ugly face under the mask ?
（丑的話）那么她剛才就死了.（還沒死）因為我偷看過了
Then she would have died. Because I peeked.
起來，我們來做一些有好玩的事情
Get up. We're going to dp something interesting.
把她帶出來
Bring her out.
有沒有想我們啊？
Did you miss us?
我們可想死你了
I know we miss you very much.
快出去
Go out, quickly
這丫頭變得越來越不聽話了The girl is getting out of hand
你應該高興才對  我們換個更好的地方
You should be happy, we are going to move to a better place.
站起來  臭婊子
Stand up bitch. Tssh.
我忘了她叫什么
我記得他叫 Ayana 或者 Ayane？
I think her name is Ayana, Ayane or something.
無所謂了
It doesn't matter.
嘛， 現在她有新名字了 肉便器
Yeah. Now she got a new name. Meat Toilet.
哈 真形象
Hah, so true.
她不是都招了嗎？你們這是干嘛？
Didn't she already told you everything ? Why do we have to do this ?
蒼馬 你難道不想一起來爽爽？
Soma. Don't you wanna have fun with us ?
我.....我已經有......
I ....I already have ...
感覺很棒吧？對吧？
how this???it's feels good.right?
我要射了，我要內射
I'm gonna cum!!! I'm about to spray your inside...
不 不要 拔出來
ahh~~!!!no!!!!pull it ouuuuut!!!!!
那還只是開始呢
And that the first one you are going to get.
哦不 他竟然內射我了
nooooooooo  he came.....inside me.....
稍等一下
Just wait a bit longer,
哦 不 不要
Don't!!! No way!!! Don't put it in again... Ahhhh!!!!
我要用精液填滿你
I'm going to fill your womb with a lots of cum
我要深入
gotta go deeper!
不 我不要這樣
no I don't want this!
照顧好我的種子
Take good care all of my semen
我又被骯臟的精液玷污了
ahhhhhh!!!!ahh!!!!I'm....I'm getting filled with dirty semen again
我要教你做性奴的愉悅
I'm going to teach your body the true happiness of being a sex slave.
我已經不辯日夜，我不知道自己還能不正常做人
I don't even know if it is night or day anymore. Will I ever get back to a normal life ?
什么聲音？
What is this sound?
什么鬼！！！
WTF
把她吊著操爽嗎
Does it fell good ? Fucking her bound to the celing ?
當然了 她不能動 我就可以更暴力地操
Yes, and since she can't move, I can get rougher
到我了
It's my turn
太爽了
this is so good!
什么鬼！！！？？？
WTF
到我了
my turn
終于到我被口了
Finally. It is my time fuck that throat.
看著你用放浪的眼神看我 讓我更爽了
Having you stare at me with those defiant eyes make even better.
我要射了 都喝下去
there...I'm cumming!drink it all properly!!
好了 放繩子 再放一點
OK. You can start lowering the rope... More... A bit more...
再放多一點
more more
羅斯
rose
羅斯 羅斯
rose rose
再放 再放
A bit more a bit more
誰想第一個上
Who wants to be first？
我我我
me me me
我今晚要插爆她的櫻桃小嘴
all right.I'm gonna pop her cherry mouth
張嘴
open your fucking mouth.
看你能撐多久
I wonder how many seconds you can last like this!
（數數）看樣子她暈過去了
1...2...3....4....5......22 ...23....thirty four! oh! looks like she fainted hum?
她比昨天多堅持了7秒 不是嗎
that was seven seconds longer than yesterday isn't it?
她絕對是吉原的女妓 她的小嘴包裹著我最敏感的部分 她的舌頭在不停攪動
She really is a prostitute from Yoshiwara. Even unconscious, her lips are around my dick most sensitive spots and her tongue keep stirring.
當然了 她口過的比別的女的多多了
Of course, she sucked more dicks than most of the girls, you'll ever see.
我要去排隊了
I am going to line up there.
我也要去
Me too
我喜歡年輕姑娘
I love young girl
我也是 我就算剛射 一看到羅斯的年輕肉體我就又硬了
Even if I just came, when I see Rose's young I get erect again.
小羅斯 都喝下去
little Rose make sure to drink it all!
今晚完成作業前你可別想休息
You can't rest until until you finish all your homework tonight.
我都干了什么 不！！！
What have I done ? Noooo !!!!
我要把Ayane調教成婊子
I'M training Ayane to become a bitch  hahahaahh
我要射進你的子宮以作為你“學習”進步的獎賞
I will cum in your womb as a reward for that excellent Learning progress
謝謝你 我里面又癢又熱
thank you very much master. It's stinky and hot
看呀 Ayane的小穴屁股都盡收眼底了 來啊 介紹一下你自己
Look! ayane's ass and pussy are in plain view! c'mon introduce yourself!
Ayane是個被這個男人養的騷婊子，被傳授內射的愉悅
fuah......Ayane is....A slutty bitch kept by this man....to be taught the pleasure of being coming inside
很好 過來
hi. come on!
是的 主人
Yes master
口！
suck it
成為令人敬畏的人的肉便器我很榮幸
I'm glad I become a cum dumpster for such horrible men ....
用力吸 賤人
suck hard bitch!
我要把她變成摯愛吸屌的變態
I will make her become a pervert who loves sucking cock  hahah
打她屁股我就能感受到她口里的震顫
When you're spanking her ass, I can feel her convulsions through her mouth.
吸完了就到這來 快點
If you're finished, come over here. Hurry up.
好的主人 這次您想讓我怎樣效勞
yes .master Where do you want me ？this time？
我剛剛射進了你的子宮 我現在要爆你的菊
I just came inside your womb. This time I want cum in your asshole.
好的
yes.
但你的屌太大了
but your dick is so big
我實在無能為力
I'm out my limit
別坐著不動 快動
Hey!don't just sit there! start moving!
給 用手
Here, use your hands too.
我感到她里面在瘋狂收縮
I feel her twitching like crazy inside
沒時間休息 我們還有好多事情要做
no time to rest. We still have a lot of thing to do
Ayane, 狗爬后入感覺怎么樣
Ayane. How does it fell doggie style ?
和我啪啪啪仿佛我是條狗
Having sex with me like I'm a dog
被其他男人的看著感覺怎么樣
Being stared at by other men with wretched eyes
太羞恥了 主人
it's embarrassing....master
那我們就要更多調教你了 知道你完全墮落
We need to train you more. Until you have completely fallen.
主人 我有沒有變成你想要的那種婊子
Master have I become a bitch the way you want?
來來來，夾緊點
Come on, squeeze me harder
好姑娘，你夾得我的屌好緊 女忍者不是浪得虛名啊
Good girl. Ohh you're coiling around my cock. They don't call you Kunoichi for nothing!
我喜歡看強硬的女人在我胯下崩潰
I like to see strong woman crumbling before me.
我好奇你的表情有多淫蕩
I wonder what lewd expression you have.
主人 我有沒有變成你想要的那種婊子
Master have I become a bitch the way you want?
當然，你現在正變成超級騷貨婊子
Yeah, you're turning into a magnificent vulgar slut
是的 感謝您讓我知道做愛這么爽
yes I....am grateful that you taught me that sex is such a pleasurable thing
兄弟 現在能把她當我們專屬RBQ了
Bro, you can treat her as our own now!
啊啊 太舒服 太刺激了
ahhhh!!!!ahhh!! amazing!he's so intense
好的 我會盡全力插你
yeah! I will go at as hard as i can!
操 太舒服了 就好像在被野獸操
fuck it's so good!It's like I am being raped by a beast....
我的子宮在顫抖 主人 求你
my womb is shivering! Ahhh!!!ahhh master please...
啊啊 主人 求求你
Ahhh!!!ahhh master please...
用你的精液沖刷別人的精液
flood the other men's sperm....with yours
好的 我會把他們的擠出來 再把你填滿
hmph.I will scrape out theirs and creampie you
我愛做愛
I love having kinky sex!!
我會把你灌滿的
I am gonna pump you full of baby juice.
給，一起去休息
Here you go. We're going to go to sleep too.
我要休息一整天
I am gonna sleep for the whole day.
我真的很抱歉 但是請聽我說
I am sorry ! But please listen to me.
羅斯....
Rose
太多男人以前背叛過我，我該習慣了
A lot of men have betrayed me before. I should have been used to it by now.
求求你開門吧 我能解釋
Open the door, please. I can explain.
我真的想讓你過的更開心
I really wanted to give you an happier life.
我從前幻想過快樂 現在看來只是水中倒影罷了
I have dream about happiness, but for me it is only as real the reflection on the water.
我會想到辦法的 相信我
I will think of another ways. Believe me.
求求你滾吧
Go away please.
哦 誰能真正愛護我
With a past like mine, who could really love me ?
蒼馬先生
ah！mistress souma
女天狗夫人
ah！mistress Nyotengu
你不介意的話 可不可以來我的房間
Mr Soma. If you don't mind, can you please come to my room ?
看起來你已經知道發生了什么
It seems you already know what's going on.
別緊張 我這么做全憑我自己的意志
Do not be nervous. I am doing this completely on my own free will.
我也請求大輝把我從吉原贖了出來
I also asked Daki to redeem me from yoshiwara.
I'm sorry I got Rose involved into this.
我很抱歉把羅斯也牽扯進來
別自責 是我要求大輝贖羅斯的
Don't blame yourself. It's me who adviced Daiki to redemn her.
那你打算怎么...啊...
So what are you planning to... ah!!!
小心
ah careful
沒事 我自己撿
It's ok, I pick it up myself.
這些刀傷？
These knife marks！？
這..emm...
ahhhh,,,,,,,,,this....
您自己弄的？抱歉在休息時叨擾 我走了
Made them to yourself ? I'm sorry to bother during your time of rest. I will leave.
路上小心
Ah... Please be careful on your way.
別，我都還沒濕
No more. Please. I am not even wet yet.
我還沒濕啊
I am not even wet yet.
沒事 我帶了新的潤滑劑
It doesn't matter. I brought a new lubricant.
這可以幫你更快進入狀態
This should help you enter quickly in the right state of mind.
這里面還有酒精成分
It also contains aphrodisiac substances.
我給她灌滿了潤滑
I pumped her asshole full of lubricant.
女人，想被夾在中間嗎
Hey girl, do you want sandwiches?
酒后操女人最醒酒了
Fucking a girl after drinking is the most refreshing
告訴我們你更喜歡誰的屌
Tell us which Dick do you like the most.
兄弟 她是不是昏過去了
Hey Bro I think she's already fainted.
不可能 她才剛剛開始
no way  I was just about to begin
你感受到她里面的收縮了嗎
Do you fell her twitching inside ?
是的 你也感覺到了？
yes Do you feel it too?
是這樣嗎 那我們得更用力沖刺了
Is that so? I'll just have to thrust even harder then!!
兄dei，我怎么操都不倦啊
Oh man, I'll never get tired of this.
我也是
Yeah me too
羅斯妹妹 你在嗎 我是女天狗
Sister Rose are you here? It's me Nyotengu
這么早，怎么了 姐姐
Ah. This is so early. What happened sister ?
你能陪我散散步嗎
Can you walk with me?
（黎明）從前吉原曾在一場大火里覆滅
Once Yoshiwara was burn down to ashes by a bigfire.
你現在看到的都是之后重建的
What you see here, is Yoshiwara after a later reconstruction.
什么樣的火
What kind of fire？
大火
A great fire.
吉原歷史上被燒過好多次
Yoshiwara has burnt several times in the past.
這是哪？
What is this place ?
這是吉原神廟 位于現在的吉原之外
This is the Yoshiwara Shrine. It is now located outside Yoshiwara current location.
這些墓碑呢？
What are these tombstones?
這些都屬于死在吉原的女妓
These are the gravestones of all prostitute who died in Yoshiwara
這太可怕了 女天狗姐姐
It sounds horrible sister Nyotengu
這些都屬于死在吉原的女妓
These are the gravestones of all prostitute who died in Yoshiwara
這些神明在她們的宿命之地守護著她們的靈魂
These gods guard their souls in what can be considered their final destination.
這是我母親的墓
This is my mother's grave.
我生在吉原里,. 南無阿彌陀佛 我堅信佛祖 愿你在極樂凈土安居
So I was born  in Yoshiwara. namas amitabha, I put my trust in Amitabha. May you be in the Pure Land of Bliss
我不想淪落的和她們一樣 所以我選擇離開吉原
I didn't want to end up like them. So I choose to leave yoshiwara.
但是代價呢？成為大輝那種混蛋的工具？
But at what price ? Being used as a tool by that cocksucker Daiki ?
我知道我只是她的工具 但是他已經簽了大量合同 這些資源可以把許多家庭帶離貧困 如果每個家庭都有飯吃 就不會有那么多父親被迫賣女兒了
I know he's using me like a tool . But he successfully signed a large number of contracts. These large amounts of foreign assets will take many families out of poverty. If every family has enough rice, not as many father would be forced to sell their daughters.
這些女孩不會斷送在吉原里 她們將有自由去愛
These girls won't end up at Yoshiwara? They won't be like us. They will be able to choose the boy they love.
用我的身體是我唯一能做的了
Using my own body is the only thing I can do.
但是 羅斯 你還年輕 當我看那些男人看我的眼神 我知道我老了
But Rose, you are still young. When I see myself into the eye of those men, staring at us, I know I am already old.
別說這些話 你可是吉原的一代狂花 現在我能理解你了 女天狗姐姐
Don't talk and act Iike you're old in front of me. You are Yoshiwara's queen of flowers. Now, I understand you better, Sister Nyotengu
歡迎各位 今晚的表演是女體之宴。新鮮的壽司刺身正擺在兩位美麗女子身上
Welcome everyone. The show tonight is Nyotaimori. There is fresh sushi and two beautiful girl everyone love
最后 祝大家胃口大開 享受女體之宴吧
Finally, I wish everyone "Bon Appetit". Enjoy your Nyotaimori.
刺身和羅斯細膩皮膚的組合簡直絕了
The combination of Rose's delicate skin and sushi is perfect
我簡直無法抵抗海鮮的味道
I can't resist the smell of seafood.
大家開動吧
so enjoy it!
我喜歡這逼的造型
I like this shape of pussy
我對這新面孔很感興趣
I am curious about this unfamiliar face
小姑娘 我們要開動了哦
Hey little girl we're going to start
別動 別動
Don't move. Just stay perfectly still.
你的乳頭挺起來了
Your little nipple is erect.
讓我們來看看你的小鯰魚
Let's look at your catfish.
我喜歡這個逼
讓我們來看看 哇哦
Let's look at your stamens wooooooo～～～
哇 我每個褶皺都看得一清二楚
Woooo I got a clear view of every wrinkle.
這個波谷好柔軟
This twin valleys are very soft
沾上妹汁的刺身最好吃了
Sushi with girl juice are delicious.
你知道么 刺身也會改變妹汁的味道
You know, The food the girl eat also change the taste of her juice.
那是什么？...哦....不要....請對我紳士一點....哦.....不要....
What's that?  no.....please......I can't bear that 。。。no。。。be a little bit gentle with me  no.....please......
哦 不要...讓我走
ooh no  no let go
對不起 大輝大人 對不起 女天狗姐姐
Sorry Daiki sama Sorry Nyotengu sister....
來人 再拉去調教
Someone ! Punish and train her again.
女天狗 今晚的表演就靠你了
Nyotengu Today's program will depend on you
好的
yes.
你怎么這么不中用 輕易毀了女體之宴
How can you be so incompetent and fail nyotaimori so easily?
計數
counting
27下
twenty seven
啊 39下
ah thirty nine
瑪麗羅斯...
Marie rose......
42下
forty two
來 讓我看看你怎么走路
come on! show me how you move
站起來 站直了 賤人
stand up. Straight up  bitch
她們的妹紙把繩子都浸透了 .她們一定愛死這繩子了
Their flow of Kinky juice got the ropes all wet. They must love this rope so much
別讓她們消停 繼續 調教她們到能用為止
Don't let the girls stop. Continue to make them work it.
我的屁股 摩擦得好...
My buts there rubbing so....
我不用你提醒我怎么做
Yeah. I don't need your advice to do that.
感覺好奇怪
it feels so strange
好久不見 想死我了 到這很久了？
Hey Long time no see. I was dying to see you! Been here long?
蒼馬 嗨
Hey souma
喝點什么？
Would you like something to drink?
加冰雞尾酒
Cocktail without ice
收到
ok
Helena，該你秀一波了，今天該我們打敗他了
Helena. Now is your time to shine. We are going to beat them now.
歡迎來看今天的表演
Welcome to today's show
請在前排找位置坐下，從她身上找樂子
Please take a seat in the front row and have fun with her body.
這些姑娘都提前下過藥了 我們提前準備好了。
These girl are specially trained with drugs. We have already prepared in advance
他們都調教好了 今晚好好享受
They were all retrained so Please have fun tonight
羅斯 展示下你的訓練成果
Rose, show them the result of yuour training.
好的 主人
yes master
（回憶）蒼馬大人 你會贖我自由嗎？
So soma sama, you will buy my freedom?
我想感謝今晚到場的客人來看我這個淫蕩的婊子
I.. I want to thank all the guest for showing up... to see a perverted bitch like me...
我是瑪麗羅斯
I'm mray rose
別趴著了 開始吧
Don't just crawl down. Let's get started
記得我們怎么教的吧？
Remember how we taught you !!!
記得
YES
一個婊子 你除了指望她舔屌之外還能指望什么
What could you expect from a whore who has milked a thousand dicks ?
她好像在用我最喜歡的深喉
she seems to be using a deep throat method that I would love to experience!
來 怎么樣 喜不喜歡被攪弄
Here! How do you like being spitroasted ?
你在等什么 快點 吸屌
What are you waiting for?  Hurry! Suck some dick.
抱歉 我來
sorry I'm go
來 羅斯 舔我的大屌
oh!Rose come on suck on my Magnum
對咯 用舌頭舔它
that's it. Lick the head with your tongue
你看看吧 這兩個妓女眼里全是要我們射的渴望 他們遲早要崩壞
just look at this ! Those two whores are possessed with an unholy need to cum! It's only a matter of time before she breaks!
到我屌這來 塊吸 吸 吸
shit!!!back to my cock! suck!suck!suck!
她嬌小的容貌真是恰到好處 小嘴里塞滿了大屌
and her beloved apprentice is going at it as well!her tiny mouth is full of big dick!
我在想這次懷的是誰的孩子
I wonder from whom this baby will be this time ?
我們怎么知道 反正大家就是瘋狂操 管他的呢
How could we know that ? Everyone is just supposed to fuck them to get them pregnant. It is fine by me
她們的喉嚨讓我的大屌抽動不已，真他媽爽
these throats are making me twitch so much, feels fuck
啊 完事了
We get all done
我站不住了，哦，不要....
Ahhh can't stand....please hel....nooooo
來 我們走近點 讓客人們大飽眼福
Let's get her closer, for our guest viewing pleasure.
你可沒時間操心別人
You don't have time to care for others.
看看這些羅斯沒照顧的大屌
Look at these dicks Rose didn't take care of.
你要替她完成工作
You got to pick up her slack.
來吧 你會愛上爆操的
come on! you sure love getting fucked hard!
啊 爽的難以置信 羅斯的里面好緊致 絕了
Amazing.....Rose insides are wrapping around me! It feels incredible!
我們都要內射你 要找到你這么個好穴可真是不容易
We are still going to keep cumming in you. It is hard to find hole as good as your in a gangbang.
你沒事吧 蒼馬
Are you okay?Soma
（回憶）我覺得我太幸福了 因為我現在能這樣抱著你
I think I'm a fortunate girl cause I can hold your body like this right now
希望你享受我的身體 你等的太久了
I hope you will enjoy my body you waited for it so long
我希望那是我們共同的夢想
I hope it's everything you dreamed with me
喝酒 別瞎雞兒想了
Forget it and drink up!
柔情是把我從這個地獄拯救的王子
Gentle is a prince who came rescue me form this hell
夠了！
Stop it enough
你沒事吧 你看起來很憔悴
Are you all right? You look dreadful..
小心
Look out
看起來羅斯小妹妹又找到感覺了
ohh~looks like being a bitch Rose-chan
加快速度 舌頭卷起來
pick up the pace and wriggle your tongue some more!
我們要操到天亮 誰想下一個上？
We are going to fuck theirs holes until steam cloud rise up ! Now who want to be next ?
她好像已經迷離了 別告訴我你最喜歡被大屌們包圍
It's like she's in a trance!Don't tell me you enjoy being coated in cum?
求求你了 主人 讓我...
Please master, let me...
姐姐
sister
也享受你雄壯的大屌
have some of your hard cocks too...
有錢 我想上誰就上誰 這就是吉原的規矩
with this money I can have sex with anyone!this is rule of yoshiwara!
不放開我
不 不 不 不要插進來
No no don't push it in
我要給這婊子多點我惡臭的精液
I will be giving this hrony bitch so much of my smelly sperm...
不 不 不 不要插進來
No no don't push it in
等下就是群交了 我們會邀請觀眾們也參與進來
the next scene will be a gangbang in which we ask the audience to participate.
女天狗可真是杰出的妓女
Nyotengu-chan really is one of the more voluptuous erotic whore in the cast
看啊 她被我們的老二弄的欲仙欲死 我從頭到尾都超性奮
Look! She's mesmerized by our little boys! Mine has been excited the whole time
看她淫蕩的臉，哪有女人在群交的時候會有這種表情
Look! What a perverted women. Who's having a face like that while being gang-banged.
你說呢 她倆都很有天賦 不是嗎
What do you think ? They are both talented right ?
加快了 后面還排著隊等著呢
Do it faster! There's still many people waiting at the back
這也太多了吧
That's too much
我受不了了
I  can't take it anymore
女天狗醬 好爽啊
Nyotengu-chan it felt great
我真的做不動了..
Please I can't take it I can't take it more
大家追隨心聲吧
please enjoy your heart's content
啊 我的頭
Ahhhh!!!My head!!!
接下來怎么辦
What do we do next ?
一把火燒干凈
Let's burn up all this old system
把吉原燒了 然后釋放所有女妓
We're going to put Yoshiwara on fire and release of all the prostitutes.
然后我們趁亂襲擊大輝的城堡
And during the chaos that ensue, we will storm Daiki's castle.
我終于找到你了 羅斯大小姐
I finally found you Rose o Jiao SA ma
讓我們燒近這罪惡 然后開創新的天地
Let's burn this evil and Create a new era together
大火之后
After the fire
羅斯躲進了日本的英租界
Rose is hiding in the Japanese British concession.
你知道嗎 小寶貝
Are you aware my dear
這世界可不止日本
The world is much more than Japan
事實上 地球很大
The earth is huge, in fact
可不是個平面
Not a flat surface
而是個空間
But is sphere
跑步的喘氣
春馬
Haruma
羅斯！\Rose
吉原出事了
Yoshiwara had an accident
就在羅斯動身離開日本前往歐洲的時候
Just before Rose leave for Europe from Japan
一個事件爆發了
a new incident break out.
政府認為
The government believes
吉原的女妓們放火燒了吉原
the prostitutes set Yoshiwara on fire
現在正準備公開處刑
and now preparing for a public trial.
羅斯能平安到達歐洲
Can Rose reach Europe safely（絕對不能
并繼承她祖母的傳奇嗎
And inherit her grandmother's legacy?（當然不能···
吉原羅斯
第三章
革命之火